[With English subtitles]
[영어 자막 있음]
This is the near future.
이것은 가까운 미래입니다.
Gene editing technology is developing rapidly.
유전자 편집 기술은 빠르게 발전하고 있습니다.
A scientific life form called a "humanoid"
'휴머노이드'라 불리는 과학적인 생명체
has been created.
생성 된.
Physiological Structure of Humanoids
휴머노이드의 생리적 구조
Almost the same as humans.
인간과 거의 같습니다.
the only difference
유일한 차이점
are the neurons in their brains
그들의 뇌에 있는 뉴런이다
Gene editing has been done in some way.
유전자 편집은 어떤 방식으로든 이루어졌습니다.
They have a single original obsession that they must abide by.
그들은 반드시 지켜야 할 하나의 독창적인 집착을 가지고 있습니다.
They can be loyal spouses until the end of their lives.
그들은 삶이 끝날 때까지 충성스러운 배우자가 될 수 있습니다 .
They can be docile and filial children.
유순하고 효도적인 자녀가 될 수 있습니다.
They can become employees who are loyal to their bosses.
상사에게 충실한 직원이 될 수 있습니다.
These custom-made humanoids begin circulating
맞춤 제작된 휴머노이드가 유통되기 시작합니다.
as a commodity on a global scale.
세계적인 규모의 상품으로서.
Even in some producing countries
일부 생산국에서도
Selling humanoid robots is illegal,
휴머노이드 로봇을 판매하는 것은 불법입니다.
There are still lawless people
아직도 불법자들이 있군요
who brought
누가 가져왔어
Humanoids entering their country without permission
허가 없이 자국에 입국하는 휴머노이드
and sell them secretly.
그리고 비밀리에 팔아요.
With the widespread spread of humanoid creatures,
인간형 생물이 널리 확산되면서,
Their risks gradually became apparent.
그들의 위험은 점차 명백해졌습니다.
more and more people
점점 더 많은 사람들
Become addicted to
중독되다
Fake emotions provided by humanoids.
휴머노이드가 제공하는 가짜 감정.
As for the humanoids themselves,
휴머노이드 자체에 관해서는,
their thoughts and emotions
그들의 생각과 감정
easily transformed
쉽게 변형됨
Within the limits of initial obsession.
초기 집착의 제약 내에서.
Many vicious events occurred as a result.
그 결과 많은 악랄한 사건이 발생했습니다.
Facing the increasingly severe situation,
점점 심각해지는 상황 에 직면하여 ,
The international community quickly convened a meeting.
국제사회는 신속하게 회의를 소집했습니다.
Humanoid robot production bans and recalls
휴머노이드 로봇 생산 금지 및 리콜
Passed unanimously.
만장일치로 통과되었습니다.
According to the agreement,
합의에 따르면,
All countries will immediately stop producing humanoid robots.
모든 국가는 즉시 휴머노이드 로봇 생산을 중단할 예정이다.
They should also recall and centralize management
또한 관리를 리콜하고 중앙 집중화해야 합니다.
All humanoids in their country.
자국의 모든 휴머노이드.
Xin Genomics Institute
신 유전체학 연구소
It was soon established in Xiyuan City.
곧 Xiyuan City에 설립되었습니다.
It's to cooperate with the police
경찰에 협조하는 것입니다
Find and identify our country's humanoid creatures.
우리나라의 인간형 생물을 찾아 식별해 보세요 .
However, the process was not smooth.
그러나 그 과정은 순탄하지 않았다.
The only way to identify humanoids
인간형을 식별하는 유일한 방법
Just inject identification drugs
그냥 식별 약물을 주입
Then observe whether the pupils change color.
그런 다음 눈동자의 색이 변하는지 관찰합니다.
But there are still flaws in identifying drugs.
그러나 약물 식별에는 여전히 결함이 있습니다.
It is very harmful to ordinary people.
그것은 보통 사람들에게 매우 해롭다.
Therefore, its use is strictly restricted.
따라서 그 사용은 엄격히 제한됩니다.
Until now,
지금까지,
five years have passed
5년이 지났다
After the humanoid ban was enacted.
인간형 금지령이 제정된 후.
There are still some humanoids
아직 휴머노이드가 좀 있네
[bionic life]
[바이오닉 라이프]
living among us.
우리 가운데 살고 있습니다.
[episode 1]
[에피소드 1]
[Xin Genomics Institute]
[신유전체학연구소]
[Investigation Group Three]
[조사3반]
Sorry I'm late.
미안 늦었 어.
What's happening here?
여기서 무슨 일이 일어나고 있는 걸까요?
Let's start.
시작하자.
deceased
고인
Is a woman.
여자입니다.
Three days ago,
3 일전,
She broke into a spa hotel armed with weapons.
그녀는 무기로 무장한 스파 호텔에 침입했습니다.
She ended up injuring a mother and her son in the room.
그녀는 결국 방에 있던 어머니와 아들에게 부상을 입혔습니다.
[The monster wields a knife late at night, and a 10-year-old boy risks his life to save his mother]
[밤늦게 괴물이 칼을 휘두르고, 10살 소년이 목숨을 걸고 엄마를 구한다]
In order to protect my mother,
어머니를 보호하기 위해,
The kid stabbed the mad woman to death.
그 아이는 미친 여자를 찔러 죽였습니다.
She fell into the fire pit
그녀는 화덕에 빠졌어요
Her face was burned.
그녀의 얼굴은 화상을 입었습니다.
The body was severely burned,
시신은 심하게 화상을 입었고,
So it cannot be identified.
그래서 식별이 불가능합니다.
The deceased was unidentified.
사망자는 확인되지 않았습니다.
And it doesn't match files that have been lost over the past few months.
그리고 지난 몇 달 동안 손실된 파일과 일치하지 않습니다.
So the police need our cooperation
그래서 경찰은 우리의 협력이 필요해요
Go through the identification process
신원확인 절차를 거치세요
Check to see if she is a humanoid.
인간형인지 확인해보세요.
Her body was severely burned
그녀의 몸은 심하게 화상을 입었다
You can't even see her pupils.
그녀의 눈동자도 볼 수 없습니다.
Of course, medicine doesn't work either.
물론 약도 효과가 없습니다.
Our job will be difficult.
우리 일은 어려울 거예요.
Even if she is in human form,
비록 인간의 모습을 하고 있지만,
She is dead.
그녀는 죽었다.
The Sheen Genome Institute does not need to be involved.
Sheen Genome Institute는 개입할 필요가 없습니다.
Right, Cheng Nuo?
그렇지, 쳉 누오?
What's the expression on this kid's face?
이 아이의 표정은 어떻습니까?
Didn't he just kill someone?
방금 사람을 죽인 게 아니었어?
No matter how mature he is,
그 사람이 아무리 성숙해도
He shouldn't be so calm.
그는 너무 침착해서는 안됩니다.
let's go.
갑시다.
We will take over the case.
우리는 사건을 인수할 것입니다.
Because of thunderstorm weather,
천둥번개가 치는 날씨 때문에,
Surveillance camera signals are affected,
감시 카메라 신호가 영향을 받습니다.
So they were on and off.
그래서 그들은 켜지고 꺼졌습니다.
I heard a loud noise
큰 소리가 들렸어요
from upstairs.
위층에서.
I checked the CCTV and something felt wrong.
CCTV를 확인해보니 뭔가 잘못된 것 같았습니다.
Then I ran up.
그런 다음 나는 달려갔습니다.
We will obtain a copy of the surveillance video.
우리는 감시 비디오의 사본을 얻을 것입니다.
no problem.
괜찮아요.
Police cordoned off the room
경찰이 방을 봉쇄했다
After they got the evidence.
증거를 얻은 후에요.
They won't let us in for now.
지금은 우리를 들여보내지 않을 거예요.
if you want to go in
네가 들어가고 싶다면
you can...
당신은 할 수 있습니다 ...
What happened to him?
그에게 무슨 일이 일어났나요?
sorry.
죄송합니다.
When the mother and son were taken away by the police,
엄마와 아들이 경찰에 연행됐을 때,
are u there?
너 거기 있어?
I was on duty in the lobby that day.
나는 그날 로비에서 근무 중이었습니다.
How is the child?
아이는 어때요?
Is he scared?
그가 겁을 먹은 걸까?
Not really.
설마.
The rooms on both sides were unoccupied.
양쪽 방은 비어 있었다.
There is a couple living in room 0210.
0210호에는 부부가 살고 있습니다.
How long were they there?
거기 얼마나 오래 있었나요?
They booked the room for 7 days.
그들은 7일 동안 방을 예약했습니다.
gentlemen.
신사.
You can't knock on the door like this.
이대로는 문을 두드릴 수 없습니다.
What are you doing? Why are you knocking so loudly?
뭐하세요? 왜 그렇게 크게 노크하는 거야?
Miss Wang, I'm sorry to bother you.
왕 씨, 귀찮게 해서 미안해요.
The two men are researchers at the Xin Genome Institute.
두 사람은 Xin Genome Institute의 연구원입니다.
They have some questions to ask.
그들은 물어볼 몇 가지 질문이 있습니다.
Aren't you done yet?
아직 안 끝났나요?
You've asked this many times!
당신은 이것을 여러 번 물었습니다!
Please repeat.
반복해주세요.
I'm telling you for the last time.
마지막으로 말씀드리겠습니다.
That day,
그 날,
I heard someone walking back and forth
누군가가 앞뒤로 걷는 소리가 들렸어요
in the corridor.
복도에서.
then i heard someone
그러다 누군가 들었어
Knock on every door.
모든 문을 두드리십시오.
after that,
이후,
I heard a loud noise.
나는 큰 소리를 들었다.
I pushed my boyfriend at that time.
그 때 제가 남자친구를 밀었어요.
He was sound asleep.
그는 곤히 잠들어 있었습니다.
Did she knock on your door too?
그 사람도 당신 집 문을 두드렸나요?
Yes.
예.
I walked near the door
나는 문 근처로 걸어갔다.
and scolded her.
그리고 그녀를 꾸짖었다.
I thought some drunkard was drunk
어떤 술취한 사람이 취한 줄 알았는데
And went to the wrong door.
그리고 잘못된 문으로 갔다.
But nothing happened after that.
그러나 그 이후에는 아무 일도 일어나지 않았습니다.
wait.
기다리다.
you mean
네 말 뜻은
She left when she heard your voice?
그녀가 당신 목소리를 듣고 떠났나요?
Yes.
예.
Thinking about it now, I'm really scared.
지금 생각해보면 정말 무서웠어요.
- she must be looking - by the way
- 그 사람이 보고 있는 게 틀림없어요 - 그런데
-Some specific goals. -when will you
-몇 가지 구체적인 목표. - 언제 할 거야?
Give me mental compensation?
정신적 보상을 해준다고?
If you don't leave I won't leave.
당신이 떠나지 않으면 나도 떠나지 않을 거예요.
Did you hear anything else?
다른 얘기도 들었나요?
after that i heard
그 후에 내가 들었어
Very loud noise.
매우 시끄러운 소음.
I also heard a woman scream,
여자의 비명소리도 들렸다.
“Let go of my child.
“내 아이를 놔주세요.
Let go of my child! "
내 아이를 놔주세요! "
Since you and the people from Xin Genomics Institute are here,
당신과 Xin Genomics Institute의 사람들이 여기에 있기 때문에
Is that crazy woman in human form?
저 미친 여자가 인간의 모습을 한 걸까요?
——He must have killed that person ——Cheng Nuo.
——그 사람이 그 사람을 죽였나 봐요 ——쳉누오.
To save his mother.
그의 어머니를 구하기 위해.
Stop making wild guesses.
엉뚱한 추측은 그만하세요.
Thanks.
감사해요.
You have come a long way to get here.
여기까지 오기 위해 먼 길을 오셨습니다.
here.
여기.
But I don't think I can help you
하지만 난 당신을 도울 수 없을 것 같아요
with what you asked.
당신이 요청한 것과 함께.
we just doubt
우리는 의심할 뿐입니다
The person who attacked you that day
그날 당신을 공격한 사람
Possibly a humanoid.
아마도 휴머노이드 일 것입니다.
Humanoid?
휴머노이드?
I have no idea.
나는 모른다.
I am really scared.
정말 무서워요.
I've told you all I can remember.
제가 기억할 수 있는 것은 모두 말씀드렸습니다.
Ms. Chen,
첸 씨,
Where is your son?
네 아들 어딨어?
We want to see him.
우리는 그를 보고 싶어요.
sorry.
죄송합니다.
He is sleeping.
그는 자고 있습니다.
It was not easy for him to fall asleep.
그에게는 잠들기가 쉽지 않았습니다.
Do you want to talk to him?
그 사람과 얘기하고 싶나요?
I know everything he knows.
나는 그가 아는 ​​모든 것을 알고 있습니다.
Can I tell you?
내가 말해도 될까요?
certainly.
틀림없이.
can you tell us
우리한테 말해줄래?
What happened when you were attacked the day before yesterday?
그저께 공격을 받았을 때 무슨 일이 일어났나요?
Yuan won second place in the piano competition.
Yuan은 피아노 콩쿠르에서 2위를 차지했습니다.
I agreed
나는 동의했다
Take him to a hot spring hotel to stay for two days.
이틀 동안 머물기 위해 그를 온천 호텔로 데려가세요.
Did you have fun today?
오늘은 즐거웠나요?
Yes.
예.
Have sweet dreams.
좋은 꿈 꾸세요.
who is it?
누구야?
Let go of my child.
내 아이를 놓아주세요.
Let go of my child!
내 아이를 놔주세요!
Yuan, run!
위안, 달려라!
This is what happened.
이것이 일어난 일입니다.
Who do you think she is?
그녀가 누구라고 생각하세요?
Why did she attack you?
그녀는 왜 당신을 공격했나요?
tramp?
도보 여행가?
or
또는
People in mental hospitals?
정신병원에 있는 사람들?
A humanoid, as we suspected?
우리가 생각했던 것처럼 인간형?
But it doesn't matter.
그러나 그것은 중요하지 않습니다.
If she were in human form
만약 그녀가 인간의 모습이었다면
It will be easier for us to deal with her.
우리가 그녀를 다루는 것이 더 쉬울 것입니다.
Ms. Chen,
첸 씨,
you know
알잖아
What do we do, right?
우리는 무엇을 할까요?
Xin Genome Institute.
신 게놈 연구소.
You specialize in humanoids.
당신은 인간형에 특화되어 있습니다.
then you should know
그럼 너도 알아야 해
The dangers of humanoids, right?
휴머노이드의 위험성, 그렇죠?
Ms. Chen,
첸 씨,
Is there anything else you want to tell us?
우리에게 더 하고 싶은 말이 있나요?
You'd better do it now.
지금 하는 것이 좋습니다.
I have nothing more to say.
더 이상 할 말이 없습니다.
sorry.
죄송합니다.
I need to cook for my kids.
나는 아이들을 위해 요리를 해야 해요.
[Please trust humans again] [We will take you home]
[다시 인간을 믿어주세요] [집으로 데려다드리겠습니다]
Let go of my child.
내 아이를 놓아주세요.
Let go of my child!
내 아이를 놔주세요!
Hello.
안녕하세요.
We are researchers at the Xin Genome Institute.
우리는 Xin Genome Institute의 연구원입니다.
We would like to ask Fang Yuan some questions.
Fang Yuan에게 몇 가지 질문을 하고 싶습니다.
I need to check with his parents.
그 사람 부모님한테 확인해 봐야겠어
Please wait.
기다리세요.
Cheng Nuo.
쳉 누오.
Fang Yuan.
팡 위안.
We are researchers at the Xin Genome Institute.
우리는 Xin Genome Institute의 연구원입니다.
No introduction is needed to us.
우리에게는 소개가 필요하지 않습니다.
We've met before.
우리는 전에 만난 적이 있어요.
correct?
옳은?
Let me show you something.
뭔가 보여드리겠습니다.
Take a look.
구경하다.
Do you know this deceased person?
이 죽은 사람을 아시나요?
can you speak?
당신은 말할 수?
Hey.
여기요.
Why are you completely unresponsive?
왜 전혀 반응이 없나요?
Cheng Nuo.
쳉 누오.
what are you doing here?
여기서 뭐하는거야?
How could you break in here?
어떻게 여기에 침입할 수 있었나요?
What are you going to do to him?
그 사람에게 무엇을 할 건가요?
I just asked him a few questions.
나는 그에게 몇 가지 질문을 했습니다.
about what?
무엇에 대해?
My son's actions were self-defense.
내 아들의 행동은 정당방위였습니다.
He didn't do anything wrong.
그는 아무 잘못도 하지 않았습니다.
Stop pestering him.
그를 괴롭히지 마세요.
We will cooperate with the police to find out the truth
경찰에 협조해 진실 규명할 것"
If your son's actions were legitimate self-defense.
아들의 행동이 정당한 정당방위였다면.
Please leave.
떠나주세요.
Has he always been so silent?
그는 항상 그렇게 침묵했습니까?
go out!
나가!
Cheng Nuo, let’s go.
청 누오, 가자.
Cheng Nuo.
쳉 누오.
sorry.
죄송합니다.
Do you think it's normal for him to be like this?
그 사람이 이런 모습이 정상이라고 생각하시나요?
he didn't say anything
그는 아무 말도 하지 않았어요
Has he since that incident?
그 사건 이후로 그랬나요?
You just scared him.
당신은 그에게 겁을 주었을 뿐이에요.
He's just a kid.
그는 단지 어린아이일 뿐입니다.
He just wanted to protect his mother.
그는 단지 어머니를 보호하고 싶었을 뿐입니다.
How can you say he is a murderer?
어떻게 그가 살인자라고 말할 수 있나요?
This is not what we need to confirm
우리가 확인해야 할 것은 이것이 아니다
What if the victim is a humanoid?
피해자가 인간형이라면?
Why do you keep pestering your children?
왜 자꾸 아이들을 괴롭히나요?
Dead people cannot speak.
죽은 사람은 말을 할 수 없습니다.
They said they did not know the attacker.
그들은 공격자를 모른다고 말했습니다.
Chen Xinhui said so.
Chen Xinhui가 그렇게 말했습니다.
Fang Yuan hasn't spoken yet.
Fang Yuan은 아직 말하지 않았습니다.
does it matter?
그게 그렇게 중요한 건가?
Yes.
예.
Is it possible to solve a crime only by injuring someone?
사람을 다치게 하는 것만으로 범죄를 해결할 수 있나요?
Then you can try your method.
그런 다음 귀하의 방법을 시도해 볼 수 있습니다.
Fang Yuan,
팡 위안,
I will protect you.
내가 너를 지켜줄 께.
Mom is here,
엄마가 여기 있어요,
You don't need to worry about anything.
아무것도 걱정할 필요가 없습니다.
It doesn't matter.
그것은 중요하지 않습니다.
[Hualan Psychological Clinic]
[화란심리클리닉]
You did very well today.
오늘 정말 잘했어요.
Make sure you eat well at home.
집에서 잘 챙겨먹도록 하세요.
OK
좋아요
he is still there
그 사람은 아직 거기 있어요
Called our nanny every day.
매일 유모에게 전화를 했어요.
I see. This is just a process.
알겠어요. 이것은 단지 과정일 뿐입니다.
You should spend more time with him.
당신은 그와 더 많은 시간을 보내야 합니다.
Don't put too much pressure on him.
그에게 너무 많은 압력을 가하지 마십시오.
OK, thanks.
알았어 고마워.
goodbye.
안녕히 가세요.
Advanced.
고급의.
An Qiu.
안 치우.
sorry.
죄송합니다.
This time I came in a hurry,
이번에는 급하게 왔는데,
So I didn't tell you in advance.
그래서 미리 말씀드리지 않았어요.
It doesn't matter.
그것은 중요하지 않습니다.
What's wrong?
뭐가 문제 야?
I won’t beat around the bush.
나는 덤불 주위를 두드리지 않을 것입니다.
Here's the thing.
여기에 문제가 있습니다.
I know
알아요
you are good at
당신은 잘해요
psychological problems.
심리적 문제.
We happen to have a case
우연히 사건이 생겼어요
We would like to ask you to help us.
우리는 당신에게 도움을 요청하고 싶습니다.
Is it about humanoids?
휴머노이드에 관한 것인가요?
Yes and no.
예, 아니오.
We're not sure yet.
아직 확실하지 않습니다.
Those involved have refused to speak.
관련자들은 발언을 거부했습니다.
So I want you to take a look.
그러니 꼭 살펴보시길 바랍니다.
-Multiple sclerosis. Zhang. -I want to see my husband.
-다발성 경화증. 장 - 남편을 만나고 싶어요.
Miss Zhang, don't run!
장 선생님, 뛰지 마세요!
He is not a humanoid. He is not!
그는 인간형이 아닙니다. 그는 아니다!
You go back first.
먼저 돌아가세요.
Let me go!
날 보내줘!
It's okay, Miss Zhang.
괜찮아요, 장 선생님.
I have a lot of people here who need help.
여기엔 도움이 필요한 사람들이 많아요.
sorry.
죄송합니다.
I see.
알겠어요.
but
하지만
This case is a bit special.
이번 사건은 좀 특별해요.
The person involved was a ten-year-old child.
관련된 사람은 열 살짜리 아이였습니다.
he killed someone
그 사람이 누군가를 죽였어
To protect his mother.
그의 어머니를 보호하기 위해.
Advanced.
고급의.
An Qiu.
안 치우.
They're already inside.
그들은 이미 안에 있어요.
Let me take you inside.
안으로 데려가겠습니다.
OK
좋아요
Ms. Chen.
첸 씨.
Sit here.
여기 앉으세요.
sorry.
죄송합니다.
My colleague was too impulsive last time.
지난번에는 내 동료가 너무 충동적이었어요.
But don't worry.
하지만 걱정하지 마세요.
We will not discuss the case this time.
이번 사건에 대해서는 논의하지 않겠습니다.
we are worried
우리는 걱정된다
After experiencing these things
이런 일들을 겪고 나면
Fang Yuan was under too much mental pressure.
Fang Yuan은 정신적 압박감이 너무 컸습니다.
So I specially invited
그래서 특별히 초대했어요
Psychology expert.
심리학 전문가.
Hope she can help Fang Yuan.
그녀가 Fang Yuan을 도울 수 있기를 바랍니다.
Hello, Ms. Chen.
안녕하세요, 첸 씨.
My name is An Qiu.
제 이름은 안 치우(An Qiu)입니다.
Can I chat with Fang Yuan?
Fang Yuan과 채팅할 수 있나요?
Hello, Fang Yuan.
안녕하세요, 팡위안님.
Can I chat with you?
나랑 수다 떨 수 있니?
if you don't say no
당신이 거절하지 않으면
Can I assume this is a yes?
이것이 그렇다고 가정할 수 있습니까?
Fang Yuan.
팡 위안.
In fact, compared with this case,
실제로 이번 사건과 비교하면,
We care more about you.
우리는 당신을 더 중요하게 생각합니다.
but if you remain silent
하지만 네가 침묵한다면
We don't know how to help you.
우리는 당신을 어떻게 도와야할지 모르겠습니다.
It's okay, Fang Yuan.
괜찮아, 팡 위안.
I totally understand how you feel.
나는 당신의 기분을 완전히 이해합니다.
how about this?
이건 어때?
Let's play a little game.
작은 게임을 해보자.
We don’t need to talk in this game.
우리는 이 게임에서 말을 할 필요가 없습니다.
do you know?
당신은 알고 있나요?
I became a psychologist
나는 심리학자가 되었다
Because I have the power of the mind.
나에게는 마음의 힘이 있기 때문이다.
I have telepathy.
나에겐 텔레파시 능력이 있다.
Do you want to try it?
시도해 보시겠어요?
Let me play with you first.
먼저 나랑 놀자.
certainly.
틀림없이.
The game is very simple.
게임은 매우 간단합니다.
This game is called Black Magic.
이 게임의 이름은 블랙 매직입니다.
Ms. Chen,
첸 씨,
Please point out any position of Fang Yuan
Fang Yuan의 입장을 지적해주세요.
For Mr. Shen.
쉔 씨를 위해.
and then,
그런 다음,
I'll tell you the answer
답을 알려드릴게요
Use my telepathic powers.
내 텔레파시 능력을 사용해 보세요.
let's start.
시작하자.
Ms. Chen, you are ready to begin.
Chen 씨, 이제 시작할 준비가 되었습니다.
OK
좋아요
Did you finish it?
끝냈어?
Yes.
예.
Please cooperate with Mr. Shen.
쉔 씨에게 협조해 주세요.
no problem.
괜찮아요.
Is this this place?
이 곳인가요?
Ms. Chen pointed?
첸 씨가 지적한 건가요?
No.
아니요.
is it here?
여기야?
Then...
그 다음에...
Yes.
예.
Do you doubt it?
당신은 그것을 의심합니까?
Mr. Shen gave me some tips?
Shen 씨가 나에게 몇 가지 조언을 줬나요?
You must have discussed it beforehand
미리 의논했어야지
and agree that the fifth is the correct answer.
다섯 번째가 정답이라는 데 동의합니다.
It's not like that.
그렇지 않습니다.
Do you use your eyes to communicate?
당신은 의사소통을 위해 눈을 사용합니까?
Not really.
설마.
how about this?
이건 어때?
Let's play it again.
다시 플레이해 봅시다.
Think about your favorite dessert
좋아하는 디저트를 생각해 보세요
And only told Mr. Shen.
그리고 Shen 씨에게만 말했습니다.
I won't look at you this time either.
이번에도 당신을 보지 않을 것입니다.
hurry up.
서둘러요.
Almond jelly.
아몬드 젤리.
Fang Yuan’s favorite dessert? ? ?
Fang Yuan이 가장 좋아하는 디저트는? ? ?
ice cream?
아이스크림?
No.
아니요.
Yeah
응
Black forest cake?
블랙포레스트 케이크?
No.
아니요.
Is it almond jelly?
아몬드젤리인가요?
Yes.
예.
Do you believe me now?
이제 내 말을 믿나요?
Actually,
실제로,
In addition to telepathy,
텔레파시 외에도
I have another mental strength.
나에겐 또 다른 정신력이 있다.
I can read your mind.
나는 당신의 마음을 읽을 수 있습니다.
Do you want to try it?
시도해 보시겠어요?
I'm hungry.
배고파요.
I want to eat.
나는 먹고 싶다.
Didn't you have breakfast before coming?
오기 전에 아침을 먹지 않았나요?
I want to eat more.
나는 더 먹고 싶다.
Okay, I'll buy you something to eat.
알았어, 먹을 것 좀 사줄게.
Stay here and be a good person.
여기에 머물면서 좋은 사람이 되세요.
Do you want to continue?
계속하시겠습니까?
Actually you still want it
사실 넌 아직도 그걸 원해
Watch my telepathy.
내 텔레파시를 조심해.
Actually,
실제로,
You don't want to eat it at all.
당신은 그것을 전혀 먹고 싶지 않습니다.
You just made an excuse
방금 변명했잖아
Let her go.
그녀를 놓아 줘.
you don't want her
당신은 그녀를 원하지 않아요
Listen to your thoughts.
당신의 생각을 들어보세요.
She takes good care of you.
그녀는 당신을 잘 보살펴줍니다.
But does it also stress you out?
하지만 그것이 당신에게도 스트레스를 주나요?
but you are
하지만 너는
He is a very sensible child.
그는 매우 현명한 아이입니다.
Are you willing to understand your mother?
당신은 당신의 어머니를 기꺼이 이해하고 싶습니까?
correct?
옳은?
My mother used to be very busy at work.
나의 어머니는 직장에서 매우 바빴습니다.
She barely had time for me.
그녀는 나를 위한 시간이 거의 없었습니다.
I don't blame her.
나는 그녀를 비난하지 않습니다.
But she actually wants to spend more time with you.
하지만 그녀는 실제로 당신과 더 많은 시간을 보내고 싶어합니다.
That's why she took you to the hot spring hotel.
그래서 그녀는 당신을 온천 호텔로 데려갔습니다.
but
하지만
what happened that day
그날 무슨 일이 있었나요
Make you sad all the time.
당신을 항상 슬프게 만드십시오.
correct?
옳은?
Yuan.
원.
you are very brave.
당신은 매우 용감합니다.
You did nothing wrong.
당신은 아무 잘못도 하지 않았습니다.
You protected your mother.
당신은 어머니를 보호했습니다.
so...
그래서...
Is protecting mom the most important thing?
엄마를 지키는 것이 가장 중요할까요?
certainly.
틀림없이.
You did cheat.
당신은 속임수를 썼습니다.
I have no idea
나는 전혀 모른다
how did you do it,
넌 어떻게 그걸 했니,
But you're not telepathic at all.
하지만 당신은 전혀 텔레파시를 사용하지 않습니다.
You are here to cheat with him.
당신은 그 사람을 속이려고 여기에 왔습니다.
Yuan.
원.
Can you tell me
나에게 말해줄 수 있나요?
What about this pocket watch?
이 회중시계는 어떻습니까?
Yuan, what's wrong?
위안, 무슨 일이야?
Sorry, Miss Chen.
미안해요, 첸 씨.
Just now, he might...
지금 당장은 그 사람이 어쩌면...
Yuan.
원.
We go home.
우리는 집에 간다.
Ms. Chen.
첸 씨.
let's go.
갑시다.
Sorry, I can't be of much help.
죄송합니다. 별로 도움이 될 수 없습니다.
Your arrival is such a big help.
당신의 도착은 정말 큰 도움이 됩니다.
I think Fang Yuan does have something to say.
Fang Yuan이 할 말이 있는 것 같아요.
But maybe he has some concerns.
하지만 어쩌면 그에게는 몇 가지 걱정거리가 있을 수도 있습니다.
On the contrary, I think
오히려 제 생각에는
Chen Xinhui's reaction was a little strange.
Chen Xinhui의 반응은 조금 이상했습니다.
Did your fingers touch him?
손가락이 그 사람을 만졌나요?
what are you saying?
당신이 무슨 말을하는거야?
The game you just played.
방금 플레이한 게임입니다.
Or maybe it's a physical cue.
아니면 물리적인 신호일 수도 있습니다.
This is my partner Cheng Nuo.
이 사람은 내 파트너인 Cheng Nuo입니다.
This is my junior An Qiu.
내 후배 안치우(An Qiu)입니다.
She is a top student majoring in psychology.
그녀는 심리학을 전공하는 우수한 학생입니다.
Hello.
안녕하세요.
Or something you discussed
아니면 당신이 논의한 것
before you go in.
들어가기 전에.
The answer is predetermined.
대답은 미리 정해져 있습니다.
Stop guessing. They are all wrong.
추측은 그만하세요. 그들은 모두 틀렸습니다.
Incorrect?
잘못된?
So what is this?
그래서 이것은 무엇입니까?
Didn't you see all this?
이거 다 못 봤어?
Were you in the control room just now?
지금 통제실에 계셨나요?
You still don't understand?
아직도 이해 못하셨나요?
this is actually a game
이건 사실 게임이에요
We play a lot in therapy.
우리는 치료를 많이 합니다.
The principle is simple.
원리는 간단합니다.
Just make a mark? ? ?
그냥 표시를 하시겠습니까? ? ?
I knew it.
알고 있었어.
You must have marked your answer.
답을 표시하셨을 것입니다.
correct?
옳은?
of course not.
당연히 아니지.
The answer is always different.
대답은 항상 다릅니다.
if this were not the case
만약 그렇지 않았다면
So where do you mark it?
그럼 어디에 표시하나요?
Think about it.
생각해 보세요.
I'll see her off.
나는 그녀를 배웅할 것이다.
I have other things to do.
다른 할 일이 있어요.
What comes before the answer?
대답 앞에 무엇이 나오나요?
Think about it.
생각해 보세요.
Still thinking about the answer?
아직도 대답을 생각하고 있나요?
Do you really think I'm stupid?
내가 정말 바보라고 생각하시나요?
options before correct answer
정답 전 옵션
It's something black.
뭔가 검은색이에요.
This game is called Dark Magic, right?
이 게임 이름이 다크 매직(Dark Magic)이죠?
Are you doubting Chen Xinhui?
Chen Xinhui를 의심하시나요?
[Chen Xinhui, Chairman of Yige Xinyuan Clothing Co., Ltd.]
[Yige Xinyuan Clothing Co., Ltd. 회장 Chen Xinhui]
[Occupation: Entrepreneur]
[직업 : 기업가]
Yes.
예.
Do you remember the surveillance video?
감시 영상을 기억하시나요?
That crazy woman knocked on a lot of doors.
그 미친 여자가 문을 많이 두드렸어요.
Why is only Chen Xinhui opening the door?
왜 Chen Xinhui만 문을 여나요?
I do not think so
난 그렇게 생각하지 않아
they have no relationship
그들은 아무 관계도 없어
As Chen Xinhui said.
Chen Xinhui가 말했듯이.
look.
바라보다.
This is Chen Xinhui’s call record this year.
올해 Chen Xinhui의 통화 기록입니다.
In addition to Fang Yuan’s teachers,
Fang Yuan의 선생님들 외에도
She had almost no contact with anyone else.
그녀는 다른 사람과 거의 접촉하지 않았습니다.
perhaps
아마도
She only focuses on
그녀는 오직
On her children?
그녀의 아이들에게?
look.
바라보다.
So does she go out often?
그럼 그 사람은 자주 나가나요?
Does not match previous information.
이전 정보와 일치하지 않습니다.
Indeed.
물론.
Indeed, she goes out a lot.
실제로 그녀는 외출을 많이 합니다.
It's also true that she doesn't like leaving home.
그녀가 집 밖으로 나가는 것을 좋아하지 않는 것도 사실이다.
Chen Xinhui and husband
천신휘와 남편
Once ran a clothing trading company.
한때 의류 무역 회사를 운영했습니다.
After her husband died of illness,
남편이 병으로 세상을 떠난 후,
She is the only one who can manage it all.
그녀는 모든 것을 관리할 수 있는 유일한 사람입니다.
The profit is still quite good.
아직까지는 수익이 꽤 괜찮습니다.
However, three years ago,
그런데 3년 전,
She suddenly sold the company.
그녀는 갑자기 회사를 팔았습니다.
She never started a business again
그녀는 다시는 사업을 시작하지 않았습니다
Or work from then on.
아니면 그때부터 일하세요.
She stayed at home.
그녀는 집에 머물렀다.
certainly,
틀림없이,
The money she earned before
그 사람이 예전에 벌었던 돈이
enough to meet their daily expenses.
일일 비용을 충당하기에 충분합니다.
so,
그래서,
She suddenly changed her personality
갑자기 성격이 변했네
three years ago.
3 년 전.
Yuan.
원.
here.
여기.
Would you like some fruit?
과일 좀 드실래요?
Can I squeeze some juice for you?
주스 좀 짜드릴까요?
Have you been in contact with Chen Xinhui recently?
최근 Chen Xinhui와 연락한 적이 있나요?
Some time ago she suddenly asked me to borrow money.
얼마 전 그녀가 갑자기 나에게 돈을 빌려달라고 했다.
But I don't have that much money.
하지만 저는 돈이 그렇게 많지 않습니다.
She just gets mad at me.
그녀는 나에게 화를 낸다.
Miss Chen?
첸 씨?
She hasn't been here for a long time.
그녀는 오랫동안 여기에 없었습니다.
in the past,
과거에,
She often comes here to have dinner with her colleagues.
그녀는 동료들과 함께 저녁 식사를 하기 위해 이곳에 자주 오곤 합니다.
She hasn't finished speaking yet
그 사람 아직 말이 끝나지 않았어
The wine she keeps here
그녀가 여기에 보관하고 있는 와인
and the balance of the membership card.
그리고 회원카드 잔액.
How long has it been since you last contacted Chen Xinhui?
Chen Xinhui에게 마지막으로 연락한 지 얼마나 되었나요?
some years.
몇년.
So she didn't go back to your hometown
그래서 그 사람은 네 고향으로 돌아가지 않았어
When did your father die?
당신의 아버지는 언제 돌아가셨나요?
No, she didn't.
아니요, 그렇지 않았습니다.
Please don't mention these things again, okay?
다시는 이런 일들에 대해 언급하지 마세요. 알았죠?
They are all in the past.
그들은 모두 과거입니다.
I heard from our friends
우리 친구들한테 들었어
she sold the company
그 사람은 회사를 팔았어
and scolded her partner.
그리고 그녀의 파트너를 꾸짖었다.
Did you visit her at her home?
그녀의 집을 방문했나요?
Yes.
예.
It seems like someone lives there,
거기 사람 사는 것 같은데,
but
하지만
She didn't open the door when I went there.
내가 거기 갔을 때 그녀는 문을 열지 않았습니다.
We haven't been in contact since.
우리는 그 이후로 연락하지 않았습니다.
In about three years,
약 3년 만에,
Not only did she sell the company;
그녀는 회사를 매각했을 뿐만 아니라;
But it also fell out
그런데 그것도 빠졌다
With all relatives and friends.
모든 친척 및 친구와 함께.
She had various reasons for falling out with them.
그녀가 그들과 사이가 나빠진 데에는 여러 가지 이유가 있었습니다.
She borrowed money from a friend.
그녀는 친구들에게서 돈을 빌렸습니다.
This is understandable.
이것은 이해할 수 있습니다.
But her brother said
그런데 그 오빠가 말했지.
When her father died,
그녀의 아버지가 돌아가셨을 때,
She didn't even attend the funeral.
그녀는 장례식에도 참석하지 않았습니다.
This doesn't make sense.
이것은 말이 되지 않습니다.
Maybe she has a secret that she doesn't want others to know.
어쩌면 그녀에게는 다른 사람들에게 알리고 싶지 않은 비밀이 있을 수도 있습니다.
Cheng Nuo,
쳉 누오,
This is the autopsy result that Director Wan asked me to give you.
완 부장님께서 부탁하신 부검 결과입니다.
I knew it.
알고 있었어.
What's this?
이건 뭐죠?
This is the autopsy report of the deceased.
고인의 부검 결과입니다.
come over.
이리와.
【Evaluation Report】
【평가 보고서】
[An autopsy showed that the spleen was ruptured and lost due to a stab wound to the abdomen? ? ? 】
[부검 결과 복부에 찔려 비장이 파열되어 소실된 것으로 나타났습니다. ? ? ]
[Smoke residue was found in the lungs, indicating that a large amount of smoke was inhaled before death]
[폐에서 연기 잔류물이 발견되어 사망 전 다량의 연기를 흡입한 것으로 나타남]
According to the autopsy report,
부검 보고서에 따르면,
The deceased had been taking hallucinogenic drugs for a long time
고인은 오랫동안 환각제를 복용해 왔다.
[Blood test showed that the deceased had been taking hallucinogenic drugs for a long time]
[혈액검사 결과 고인은 오랫동안 환각제를 복용한 것으로 나타났습니다]
[The deceased had symptoms of muscle atrophy and malnutrition]
[고인은 근육 위축 및 영양실조 증상을 보였습니다]
and suffering from malnutrition
그리고 영양실조에 걸려
and muscle atrophy before death.
사망 전 근육 위축.
She was most likely imprisoned.
그녀는 투옥되었을 가능성이 높습니다.
do you remember
기억 나니
What did Ms. Wang at the hotel say?
호텔에 있던 왕씨는 뭐라고 말했나요?
Then I heard a loud noise.
그러다 큰 소리가 들렸습니다.
She said she heard someone screaming
그녀는 누군가 비명을 지르는 소리를 들었다고 하더군요
“Let go of my child.
“내 아이를 놔주세요.
Let go of my child! "
내 아이를 놔주세요! "
If we take it literally,
문자 그대로 받아들이면,
we subconsciously believe
우리는 무의식적으로 믿는다
Chen Xinhui said so.
Chen Xinhui가 그렇게 말했습니다.
But I listened carefully to the recording
그런데 녹음을 잘 들어보니
And found that something was wrong with the tone.
그리고 톤에 뭔가 문제가 있다는 것을 발견했습니다.
Let go of my child.
내 아이를 놓아주세요.
Let go of my child!
내 아이를 놔주세요!
She emphasizes "my"
그녀는 "나의"를 강조한다
Rather than "let go".
"가자"보다는.
So I think
그래서 나는 생각한다
It should be the crazy woman who said this.
이런 말을 한 사람은 미친 여자임에 틀림없다.
This is the real Chen Xinhui.
이것이 진짜 Chen Xinhui입니다.
Well, it's clear now.
이제 분명해졌습니다.
signature.
서명.
Cheng Nuo,
쳉 누오,
we shouldn't
우리는하지 말아야
Should I be more cautious before signing?
서명하기 전에 더 주의해야 합니까?
Fang Yuan is still just a child.
Fang Yuan은 아직 어린 아이입니다.
If we took away his only family
만약 우리가 그의 유일한 가족을 빼앗아간다면
I'm afraid he can't bear such a huge blow.
그 사람은 그렇게 큰 타격을 견딜 수 없을 것 같아요 .
-And, Chen Xinhui... -Are you speaking for humanoids?
- 그리고 Chen Xinhui... - 인간형을 말하는 겁니까?
have you ever thought about
생각해 본 적 있어?
What does this result mean to them?
이 결과는 그들에게 무엇을 의미합니까?
That's not what I should be thinking about.
그건 내가 생각해야 할 것이 아닙니다.
Neither do you.
너도 그렇지 않아.
You just need to judge
그냥 판단하시면 됩니다
If the target is a humanoid. that's all.
대상이 인간형인 경우. 그게 다야.
so,
그래서,
Is protecting mom the most important thing?
엄마를 지키는 것이 가장 중요할까요?
certainly.
틀림없이.
You did cheat.
당신은 속임수를 썼습니다.
I don't know how...
어떻게 해야할지 모르겠어...
Protect mom...
엄마를 지켜주세요...
[Is protecting mother the most important thing? 】
[엄마를 지키는 것이 가장 중요한가요? ]
Hello, senior.
안녕하세요, 선배님.
I want to leave the Xin Genome Institute.
저는 Xin Genome Institute를 떠나고 싶습니다.
Why?
왜?
You still remember my partner Cheng Nuo, right?
아직도 내 파트너 Cheng Nuo를 기억하시나요?
The difference between humanoids and humans
휴머노이드와 인간의 차이점
Just the initial obsession.
단지 초기 집착일 뿐입니다.
It is the basis of all behavior
모든 행동의 기본이다
and humanoid emotions.
그리고 인간형 감정.
It's like an instinct.
그것은 본능과 같습니다.
Sheen Genome Institute aims to work with police
Sheen Genome Institute는 경찰과 협력하는 것을 목표로합니다
Identify and search for humanoids.
휴머노이드를 식별하고 검색합니다.
But at the same time we also need to care for them.
하지만 동시에 우리는 그들을 돌볼 필요도 있습니다.
However, Cheng Nuo was different.
그러나 Cheng Nuo는 달랐습니다.
he has been hostile
그 사람은 적대적이야
Towards the humanoids.
인간형을 향해.
To identify humanoids,
인간형을 식별하기 위해,
He is willing to do anything.
그는 무엇이든 할 의지가 있습니다.
But humanoids
하지만 휴머노이드
Not a robot.
로봇이 아닙니다.
They look just like us.
그들은 우리와 똑같아 보입니다.
They could be any one of us.
그들은 우리 중 누구라도 될 수 있습니다.
Every time I look for humanoids
휴머노이드를 찾을 때마다
I met a group of people
한 무리의 사람들을 만났어요
Who has an emotional connection to it.
감정적으로 연관되어 있는 사람.
If the human form disappears
인간의 모습이 사라진다면
Their lives will also change completely.
그들의 삶도 완전히 바뀔 것이다.
we need to correct
우리는 바로잡아야 해
People's overreliance on humanoids.
인간형에 대한 사람들의 과도한 의존.
But this process
하지만 이 과정은
Makes me feel stressed.
스트레스를 받네요.
sorry
죄송합니다
Let you listen to my complaints.
내 불만을 들어주세요.
It doesn't matter.
그것은 중요하지 않습니다.
Advanced.
고급의.
Whether we're investigators or psychologists,
우리가 수사관이든 심리학자이든,
The purpose of our work is to enable people
우리 일의 목적은 사람들이
accept the truth.
진실을 받아들이십시오.
Some people give up on themselves,
스스로 포기하는 사람도 있고,
But we can't give up on them.
하지만 우리는 그들을 포기할 수 없습니다.
hold onto.
붙잡아라.
Maybe a turnaround will come soon.
아마도 곧 반전이 올 것입니다.
Thanks.
감사해요.
An Qiu,
안 치우,
Actually,
실제로,
I think you are better suited for this job than me.
내 생각엔 당신이 나보다 이 일에 더 적합하다고 생각해요.
wait.
기다리다.
look at this.
이거 봐요.
【Seasonal Recruitment】
【계절모집】
i saw it all
난 다 봤어
When you are talking to Fang Yuan.
Fang Yuan과 대화할 때.
If you work with Cheng Nuo,
Cheng Nuo와 함께 일한다면,
He might become different.
그는 달라질 수도 있습니다.
Really?
정말?
I thought there was nothing I could do to help.
내가 도울 수 있는 일은 아무것도 없다고 생각했다.
Incidentally,
그런데,
what is the end result
최종 결과는 무엇입니까
What about Fang Yuan’s case?
Fang Yuan의 경우는 어떻습니까?
almost finished.
거의 끝났다.
We may have final confirmation tomorrow.
내일 최종 확정이 나올 수도 있습니다.
Actually, I am still quite worried about Fang Yuan.
사실 저는 아직도 Fang Yuan에 대해 상당히 걱정하고 있습니다.
Can I take a look tomorrow?
내일 좀 볼 수 있을까요?
Mr. Shen,
쉔 씨,
A lady is looking for you outside.
밖에서 어떤 여자가 당신을 찾고 있어요.
OK
좋아요
An Qiu.
안 치우.
Why are the police here?
경찰이 왜 여기에 있는 걸까요?
Chen Xinhui is missing.
첸 신휘(Chen Xinhui)가 실종되었습니다.
what happened?
무슨 일이에요?
Chen Xinhui
첸 신휘
Identified as humanoid.
인간형으로 식별됩니다.
Where did that figure go?
그 수치는 어디로 갔나요?
I've been asking you for almost 30 minutes.
거의 30분 동안 질문을 했어요.
-You won't say anything, right? -team leader.
- 아무 말도 안 할 거지? -팀 리더.
I found a secret door in the living room.
거실에서 비밀의 문을 발견했어요.
Come and take a look.
와서 한 번 보세요.
OK future.
좋아요 미래.
Take care of Fang Yuan for me.
나를 위해 Fang Yuan을 돌봐주세요.
OK
좋아요
I knew it.
알고 있었어.
Yuan.
원.
will be easier
더 쉬울 것이다
Tell us everything.
우리에게 모든 것을 말해주세요.
Let me ask you one last time.
마지막으로 한번 물어보겠습니다.
Where is that figure?
그 피규어는 어디에 있나요?
at this point,
이 지점에서,
What are you still hiding?
아직도 무엇을 숨기고 있나요?
Could you please stop talking to children like this?
제발 아이들에게 이런 식으로 얘기하는 걸 그만둬 주실 수 있나요?
Do you know what he did?
그 사람이 무슨 짓을 했는지 아세요?
That victim was his mother.
그 피해자는 그의 어머니였다.
We've done DNA testing
우리는 DNA 테스트를 완료했습니다
For the deceased in the hot spring hotel,
온천호텔에 묵었던 고인의 명복을 빕니다.
Him, and his mother.
그와 그의 어머니.
The results show
결과는 보여줍니다
The victim was also Chen Xinhui.
피해자 역시 천신휘였다.
One of them must be a humanoid.
그 중 하나는 인간형이 틀림없어요.
You won't tell, will you?
넌 말하지 않을 거야, 그렇지?
Let me help you recall the process.
그 과정을 기억할 수 있도록 도와드리겠습니다.
I guess
내 생각엔
Your mother is too busy at work
네 엄마는 일하느라 너무 바빠
So she customized a human figure in Lao Cai
그래서 그녀는 라오까이의 인간 형상을 맞춤 제작했습니다.
Who looks exactly like her
그녀와 꼭 닮은 사람
Take care of you for her.
그녀를 위해 당신을 돌봐주세요.
her first obsession
그녀의 첫 집착
It must be good for you
그것은 당신에게 좋을 것입니다
and obey you unconditionally.
그리고 무조건 순종하세요.
stop.
멈추다.
Your mother has high hopes for you
네 어머니는 너에게 큰 기대를 갖고 계시다
This makes you feel stressed.
이로 인해 스트레스를 받게 됩니다.
That is a kind of love.
그것은 일종의 사랑입니다.
But in human eyes,
그러나 인간의 눈에는
This is a disservice.
이것은 해악입니다.
Humanoids are no longer satisfied
휴머노이드는 더 이상 만족하지 않습니다.
As a surrogate mother.
대리모로서.
She thought she was more qualified
그녀는 자기가 더 자격이 있다고 생각했어
Become your mother.
당신의 어머니가 되십시오.
Teacher Yuan, I'm going to work.
원 선생님, 저는 일하러 갑니다.
- Stay at home and listen to your aunt. -But it's not easy
- 집에 있으면서 이모의 말을 잘 들어보세요. -하지만 쉽지 않죠
to replace humans.
인간을 대체하기 위해.
first,
첫 번째,
This is just basic imitation.
이것은 단지 기본적인 모방일 뿐입니다.
Yuan.
원.
I go to work.
나는 일하러 간다.
be a good person
좋은 사람이 되세요
Listen to your aunt at home.
집에서 이모의 말을 들어보세요.
Thanks.
감사해요.
Humanoid placing drugs
인간형 배치 약물
Get into food and water every day.
매일 음식과 물을 섭취하십시오.
Gradually,
서서히,
There is something wrong with your mother's health.
어머니의 건강에 이상이 생겼습니다.
at the same time,
동시에,
She started her plan to replace her.
그녀는 자신을 대체할 계획을 시작했습니다.
Ms. Chen, are you sure you want to sell your company?
Chen 씨, 정말 회사를 팔고 싶으신 가요 ?
In order to avoid being discovered by people familiar to Ms. Chen,
첸 씨와 친숙한 사람들에게 발각되는 것을 피하기 위해,
She takes the initiative
그녀가 주도권을 잡는다
Identify areas of discord between your mother and her family and friends
어머니와 가족, 친구들 사이에 불화가 있는 부분을 확인하십시오 .
Cut ties with everyone.
모든 사람과의 관계를 끊으세요.
Can you understand me?
내 말을 이해할 수 있나요?
I'm in charge now.
지금은 내가 책임을 맡고 있어요.
I can't go back.
나는 돌아갈 수 없다.
Yuan.
원.
I've fired that nanny.
내가 그 유모를 해고했어요.
From now on I will take care of you wholeheartedly.
이제부터 성심성의껏 보살펴 드리겠습니다.
Humanoids may be afraid to kill humans.
휴머노이드는 인간을 죽이는 것을 두려워할 수도 있습니다.
So she kept your mother
그래서 그녀는 네 엄마를 지켜줬어
In the basement.
지하에.
Your mother was drugged
네 엄마가 약을 먹었어
So she is sometimes awake and sometimes confused.
그래서 그녀는 때로는 깨어 있고 때로는 혼란스러워합니다.
able...
할 수 있는...
Can I ask you a question?
질문해도 될까요?
when? ? ?
언제? ? ?
when i left,
내가 떠났을 때,
Is Fang Yuan okay?
팡위안은 괜찮아?
Is he happy?
그는 행복합니까?
Did it? ? ?
그것을했다? ? ?
Does he miss his mother?
그는 어머니를 그리워합니까?
I am his mother.
나는 그의 어머니입니다.
He is happy now.
그는 지금 행복합니다.
I won't do anything to upset him.
나는 그를 화나게 하는 어떤 짓도 하지 않을 것이다.
Drink it when you are stronger.
당신이 더 강해질 때 그것을 마신다.
On the day of the incident, there was a thunderstorm.
사건 당일에는 천둥번개가 쳤습니다.
basement door
지하실 문
I opened it myself,
제가 직접 열어봤는데,
The fault may be caused by a power outage.
정전으로 인해 오류가 발생할 수 있습니다.
【Hot Spring Hotel】
【온천호텔】
Have sweet dreams.
좋은 꿈 꾸세요.
Mom, what's wrong?
엄마, 무슨 일이에요?
It doesn't matter. Let me go and see.
그것은 중요하지 않습니다. 내가 가서 보자.
who is it?
누구야?
You took my child away. it was all your fault!
당신은 내 아이를 데려갔습니다. 그건 다 네 잘못이야!
Mother!
어머니!
Let go of my child.
내 아이를 놓아주세요.
Let go of my child!
내 아이를 놔주세요!
Yuan, run!
위안, 달려라!
You didn't kill her, did you?
당신은 그녀를 죽이지 않았죠?
This was done by humanoids.
이것은 휴머노이드에 의해 수행되었습니다.
I do not understand
난 이해가 안 돼요
Why do you still insist you did it.
왜 아직도 당신이 그랬다고 주장하는 거죠?
She has abandoned you
그녀는 당신을 버렸어요
But you still care about her.
하지만 당신은 여전히 ​​그녀를 걱정하고 있습니다.
She won't abandon me.
그녀는 나를 버리지 않을 것입니다.
why not?
왜 안 돼?
The initial obsession?
초기 집착?
Are you so sure?
정말 확신하시나요?
Her first obsession was to take care of you?
그녀의 첫 번째 집착은 당신을 돌보는 것이었습니까?
Maybe he is becoming another Chen Xinhui.
아마도 그는 또 다른 Chen Xinhui가 되어가고 있는 것 같습니다.
that's why
그렇기 때문에
she got rid of real people
그녀는 진짜 사람들을 없애버렸어
and replaced her.
그녀를 대신했습니다.
And you
당신은요
- Just the tools she uses. -nonsense!
- 그녀가 사용하는 도구만요. -무의미한 말!
This was not planned.
이것은 계획되지 않았습니다.
She didn't mean it.
그녀는 그런 뜻이 아니었어요.
Then why did you lie?
그럼 왜 거짓말을 했나요?
In the end what happened?
결국 무슨 일이 일어났나요?
Cheng Nuo.
쳉 누오.
Yuan. Do not be afraid. Do not be sad.
원. 두려워 하지마. 슬퍼하지 마.
Only by knowing the truth
진실을 아는 것만으로도
How can we help you?
어떻게 도와 드릴까요?
can you tell us
우리한테 말해줄래?
What happened that night?
그날 밤 무슨 일이 일어났나요?
Yuan.
원.
What should we do?
우리는 무엇을 해야 합니까?
I did not do it on purpose.
일부러 그런 건 아니었어요.
I don't know my mother
나는 어머니를 모른다
who is with me
나와 함께있는 사람은 누구입니까?
Until that night, she was mother in human form.
그날 밤까지 그녀는 인간의 모습을 한 어머니였습니다.
Sorry, Yuan.
미안해요, 위안.
I am too busy.
나는 너무 바빠요.
I don't have time to take care of you.
나는 당신을 돌볼 시간이 없습니다.
Here's a little gift
여기 작은 선물이 있어요
Congratulations on your win.
승리를 축하합니다.
I have lost my mother.
나는 어머니를 잃었습니다.
I just don't want to lose another one.
나는 단지 다른 것을 잃고 싶지 않습니다.
You asked me that day
그날 네가 나한테 물었잖아
If protecting mom is the most important thing.
엄마를 보호하는 것이 가장 중요하다면.
You must be blaming yourself.
당신은 자신을 비난해야합니다.
But I'm right.
하지만 내 말이 맞아요.
Yuan, you are very brave.
위안씨, 당신은 정말 용감해요.
You just protected your other mother.
당신은 방금 다른 어머니를 보호했습니다.
Another mom?
또 다른 엄마?
Having said that,
라고 한,
She left when she was needed most.
그녀는 가장 필요할 때 떠났습니다.
Yuan.
원.
She won't leave for no reason.
그녀는 아무 이유 없이 떠나지 않을 것이다.
You know what she went to do, right?
그 사람이 무슨 일을 하러 갔는지 아시죠?
Will Mom get legal status?
엄마가 법적 신분을 얻을 수 있나요?
What do you mean?
무슨 뜻이에요?
she got a call
그 사람한테 전화가 왔어
Today comes from a stranger.
오늘은 낯선 사람에게서 왔습니다.
he said he knew
그 사람은 안다고 했어
Our secret.
우리 비밀.
He can help us.
그분은 우리를 도와주실 수 있습니다.
do you know
당신은 알고 있나요
Where do they meet?
그들은 어디서 만납니까?
In Forest Park.
포레스트 파크에서.
let's break up.
헤어지자.
Chen Xinhui.
첸 신휘.
Advanced.
고급의.
stop! stop!
멈추다! 멈추다!
Boy saves his mother
소년은 어머니를 구한다
There's a surprising twist.
놀라운 반전이 있습니다.
[Xiyuan City Breaking News]
[시위안시 속보]
This ten-year-old boy relies too much on humanoids
이 10살 소년은 휴머노이드에 너무 많이 의존합니다.
He hid it from the police
그는 경찰에게 그것을 숨겼어요
The humanoid creature killed his mother for his crime.
인간형 생물은 자신의 범죄로 인해 어머니를 죽였습니다.
The patient has inhaled too much smoke,
환자가 연기를 너무 많이 흡입했고,
Causes cerebral hypoxia and ischemia.
대뇌 저산소증과 허혈을 유발합니다.
He remains in a coma.
그는 여전히 혼수상태에 빠져 있습니다.
If the coma lasts too long
혼수상태가 너무 오래 지속되는 경우
He may have sequelae.
그에게 후유증이 있을 수 있습니다.
Why don't you save him?
그 사람을 구해 주는 게 어때요?
if you hadn't run away
만약 네가 도망치지 않았다면
He might not be lying here.
그는 여기 누워 있지 않을 수도 있습니다.
I ran
나는 달렸다
Catch the suspect.
용의자를 잡아라.
Really?
정말?
Has the suspect been caught?
용의자는 잡혔나요?
for you,
당신을 위한,
Catching the suspect is more important than saving people.
사람을 구하는 것보다 용의자를 잡는 것이 더 중요하다.
correct?
옳은?
I believe Shen Li
나는 션리를 믿는다
——will make the same choice. -you are wrong.
——같은 선택을 하게 될 것이다. -당신은 잘못.
He will choose to save you.
그분은 당신을 구원하기로 선택하실 것입니다.
【Seasonal Recruitment】
【계절모집】
Hello, is this the Human Resources Department?
안녕하세요. 인사부인가요?
I would like to join the Sheen Genome Institute.
Sheen Genome Institute에 합류하고 싶습니다.